<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ShadowNode Wiki on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>/tags/shadownode-wiki/</link><description>Recent content in ShadowNode Wiki on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/tags/shadownode-wiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guides</title><link>/home/guides/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/</guid><description> Chunk Loaders Contributing Store and Perks Team Play In this category you will find all guides and answers to questions you may have about our server! As always you can also ask for help in our Discord.</description></item><item><title>Server Info</title><link>/server-info/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/</guid><description> Vote Servers Rules Staff Here you will find information about what ShadowNode is, what our policies are, and who’s on our staff team. As always you can also ask for help in our Discord.</description></item><item><title>Wiki</title><link>/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/</guid><description> Commands Guides Join our Servers Chunk Loaders In this category you will find all commands, guides, rules and answers to questions you may have about our server! As always you can also ask for help in our Discord.</description></item><item><title>Banned Items</title><link>/server-info/banned/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/banned/</guid><description>We have banned certain items on our servers because of issues in the past that now require us to disable them. If you encounter a bug, or any issue with the items, please report it in our Discord Support channel. Our plugin allows us to ban the items in a way that allows you to still progress through the pack. Craft, Place, Use, and Near are all the different ways items can be banned.</description></item></channel></rss>