<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wiki on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/</link><description>Recent content in Wiki on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basic Commands</title><link>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/commands/</guid><description>Basic Commands Argument Required &amp;lt;&amp;gt; Required [] Optional Discord In order to join discord, you need to run the command /discord in game, this will give you the invite link in your chat window.
Home These commands are affecting by your rank. For example a normal member gets only 1 home. See Ranks for more info!
/sethome [name] [-o] Sets your home at a current location.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/contributing/</guid><description>To contribute to this wiki all you need to do is follow this handy little guide! All of these steps require a Github account!
First Step There's two ways to do this:
If you just want to simply edit one of the existing pages you just click the Edit this page in the top right of the page! Then skip to Step 3
Or if you want to create a new section go to the project and click the Fork button.</description></item><item><title>Guides</title><link>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/guides/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/guides/</guid><description>Chunk Loaders Modded Chunk Loaders have been disabled on ShadowNode servers globally, therefore we have added a plugin known as Better Chunk Loaders to achieve their purpose. There are two types of Chunk Loaders, Always On and Online Only. To view chunk borders, hit F3+g
The most basic command in the plugin is /betterchunkloader, or just /bcl for short. Executing this command will open an interface in the chat that the user may interact with.</description></item><item><title>Wipes and Restarts</title><link>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/wipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shadownode.github.io/wiki/wipes/</guid><description>Servers restart every once in a while to reduce lag. This does not mean that a restart will fix all kinds of lag so, please, do not as staff to restart a server due to lag. Restarts are NOT wipes, they are just a daily reboot to the server. Ground items are cleared every 20 minutes (XX:10, XX:30, XX:50). There is a 1 minute warning before a clear.
All times listed are in Eastern Standard Time (EST).</description></item></channel></rss>