<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Modded MC Network on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>/tags/modded-mc-network/</link><description>Recent content in Modded MC Network on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/tags/modded-mc-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guides</title><link>/home/guides/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/</guid><description> Chunk Loaders Contributing Store and Perks Team Play In this category you will find all guides and answers to questions you may have about our server! As always you can also ask for help in our Discord.</description></item><item><title>How to Join</title><link>/join/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/join/</guid><description>Jump In and Join The Fun Our Server IPs Our Rules Suggested Launchers FTB App CurseForge There used to be a number of choices as to what launchers you could use to connect to servers with, however, we've curated the above links and guides to enable you to be able to connect to our servers successfully. If you need further assistance with using one of the launchers listed above please feel free to join our Discord and ask for help in the support section.</description></item><item><title>Server Info</title><link>/server-info/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/</guid><description> Vote Servers Rules Staff Here you will find information about what ShadowNode is, what our policies are, and who’s on our staff team. As always you can also ask for help in our Discord.</description></item><item><title>Wiki</title><link>/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/</guid><description> Commands Guides Join our Servers Chunk Loaders In this category you will find all commands, guides, rules and answers to questions you may have about our server! As always you can also ask for help in our Discord.</description></item><item><title>Modpack Tips</title><link>/modpack-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/</guid><description> 1.16 vs 1.12 Packs POZ3 MC Eternal Check out the links above for some of our popular tips as well as the navigation menu for more options. As always you can also ask for help in our Discord.</description></item><item><title>Legacy Info</title><link>/legacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/legacy/</guid><description>Legacy Info The information on these following pages is kept as legacy content from old servers, launchers, and guides that may no longer be valid. Please use caution when using anything within this section.</description></item><item><title>Modpack Tips</title><link>/legacy/modpack-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/legacy/modpack-tips/</guid><description>Legacy Info The information on these following pages is kept as legacy content from old servers, launchers, and guides that may no longer be valid. Please use caution when using anything within this section.</description></item><item><title>1.16 Packs</title><link>/modpack-tips/1-16_packs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/1-16_packs/</guid><description>Note This section might not always be up-to-date. Please let us know or submit changes if you discover this is the case. To find out how see contributing.
1.16 vs 1.12 Packs Many of you are already familiar with 1.12.2 and 1.16 packs but there are some key changes that seemingly impact all 1.16 packs as a whole. As a result of this you&amp;rsquo;re likely wondering what&amp;rsquo;s changed and how you can work around it.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Claim Management</title><link>/home/guides/advancedclaims/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/advancedclaims/</guid><description>Public Transit Within Claims Viaducts and Waystones are a great and fun way to get around an expansive base while not forcing the use of homes and teleportation requests to other friends and basemates! That being said, typically you would need to give them full access to inventories such as your chests, crates, ME systems, etc. You can solve this by issuing some commands that will set &amp;ldquo;flags&amp;rdquo;, these are extra settings that override the default behavior.</description></item><item><title>ATM6 Sky</title><link>/legacy/modpack-tips/atm6sky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/legacy/modpack-tips/atm6sky/</guid><description>Note This page is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Should you find it needs an update please either let us know on Discord or consider contributing to our wiki directly.
Important Rules Our OceanBlock server follows all global rules that are applicable to all of our other servers. You can find our global rules on our wiki and at /spawn.</description></item><item><title>Banned Items</title><link>/server-info/banned/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/banned/</guid><description>We have banned certain items on our servers because of issues in the past that now require us to disable them. If you encounter a bug, or any issue with the items, please report it in our Discord Support channel. Our plugin allows us to ban the items in a way that allows you to still progress through the pack. Craft, Place, Use, and Near are all the different ways items can be banned.</description></item><item><title>Chunkloaders</title><link>/home/guides/chunkloaders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/chunkloaders/</guid><description>Chunk Loaders Modded Chunk Loaders have been disabled on ShadowNode servers globally, therefore we have added a plugin known as Better Chunk Loaders to achieve their purpose. There are two types of Chunk Loaders, Always On and Online Only. To view chunk borders, hit F3+g
Always On vs Online Only Always On is a chunk loader which is online 24/7 and will keep the chunk loaded. However, the chunk loader will stop loading the chunk after 48 (1.</description></item><item><title>Claiming</title><link>/home/guides/claiming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/claiming/</guid><description>Claiming All of our servers use the latest Grief Prevention plugin for claiming.
How to Claim To claim you can either use a Golden Shovel you make, or one provide to you when you first join the server (some servers do not start with the golden shovel or have had their claim tool changed). Every block claimed is accounted for. You can buy claim blocks from the tokenshop, or from the store.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>/home/guides/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/contributing/</guid><description>Intro You might want to contribute code, content or time to this wiki and are unsure how to do so. Please follow the steps below on how to do so.
Note All of these sections mentioning GitHub require a GitHub account!
Making Suggestions for Edits If you&amp;rsquo;re not comfortable writing Markdown or using Git you can make suggestions for edits via our project&amp;rsquo;s GitHub Issues or open a ticket in our Discord detailing the changes needed.</description></item><item><title>Crash Reports</title><link>/home/guides/crash-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/crash-reports/</guid><description>Note This page is still a work in progress and has yet to be finished!
Here you will find how to get your crash report for your specific launcher of choice.
FTB Launcher Open the Launcher Select the Modpack, click on Edit Modpack and on Open Folder. Now you are in the mods folder, go back to the minecraft folder. Open the crash-reports folder. Paste the content of the latest crash-report MCLo.</description></item><item><title>Crates</title><link>/home/guides/crates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/crates/</guid><description>Crates We use a plugin called HuskyCrates to manage our crates. Crates contain items, the quality of which depends on the tier of the crate. To open a create you must hold the crate key in your hand and right click the corresponding crate. You can obtain crate keys by either purchasing them from our shop, or buy buying them in our token shop. Note Some items on this list may not be on your server as some modpacks don&amp;rsquo;t have all the mods as others.</description></item><item><title>CurseForge</title><link>/join/curseforge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/join/curseforge/</guid><description>CurseForge CurseForge is a popular Minecraft launcher. It can be used to launch vanilla Minecraft, custom Modpacks, or CurseForge Modpacks. This launcher great for getting into modded Minecraft and providing a simple expirence. However, for advanced users we&amp;rsquo;d recommend using GDLauncher or MultiMC. CurseForge works on Windows and macOS.
How to Install Head to CurseForge and download the CurseForge Beta Launcher for your OS. The steps below are taken from a Windows install so it might be different if you&amp;rsquo;re on macOS.</description></item><item><title>FTB App</title><link>/join/ftbapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/join/ftbapp/</guid><description>About FTB App FTB App is a popular Minecraft launcher brought to you by the Feed The Beast Team. It can be used to launch vanilla Minecraft, Feed The Beast (FTB), or CurseForge modpacks. This launcher great for getting into modded Minecraft and providing a simple expirence. However, for advanced users we&amp;rsquo;d recommend using GDLauncher or MultiMC. FTB App works on Windows, Linux and macOS.
How to Install Head to Feed The Beast and click on the download link for your platform.</description></item><item><title>FTB Stoneblock 2</title><link>/modpack-tips/stoneblock2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/stoneblock2/</guid><description>Note This list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our Stoneblock 2 server has some additional rules on the server apart from the global rules you find on all our servers.
Max 2 Imaginary Time Blocks. This applies per team/base/area. Max 2 Growth Crystals. This applies per team/base/area. Cows and Chickens Cows and Chickens must always be in their respective pens.</description></item><item><title>Github Gist</title><link>/home/guides/gist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/gist/</guid><description>How to Use Github Gist While other copy and paste tools, like Pastebin or Hastebin, are more popular then Github Gist, Github Gist is one of the better copy and paste tools. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a character count and it&amp;rsquo;s just as easy to use as other tools. Using a copy and paste tool like Gist is recommended if you have issues with client crashes since it keeps the formatting of the log, and makes it easier to read the file without having to download it.</description></item><item><title>Launchers</title><link>/legacy/launchers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/legacy/launchers/</guid><description>Legacy Info The information on the following pages is kept as legacy content from past guides that may no longer be valid. Please use caution when using anything within this section.</description></item><item><title>Managing Mods</title><link>/home/guides/managing-mods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/managing-mods/</guid><description>Managing Your Mods Warning Removing and adding mods can cause pack instability. Please consult your launcher&amp;rsquo;s documentation on backing up your instance prior to preforming any of the tips below.
Modded Minecraft is great and there&amp;rsquo;s tons of mods you likely have in your modpacks you play every day and are unaware of. In fact, there&amp;rsquo;s often a few bundled mods in packs that simply add bloat, don&amp;rsquo;t provide any functionality to the end user and in the end are simply unnecessary to play the pack.</description></item><item><title>Market</title><link>/home/guides/market/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/market/</guid><description>Note This mod only works on our Modded 1.12 servers
The Market The market plugin is a custom plugin that allows you to buy/sell/trade items in a text-based marketplace. Running /market help in game will return a list of commands.
How to Access the Market To view the current listings, type the command /market How to buy an item You can either browse the market or you can click on the Search Seller button to find a specific player&amp;rsquo;s listening.</description></item><item><title>MC Eternal</title><link>/modpack-tips/mc-eternal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/mc-eternal/</guid><description>Note This list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our MC Eternal server follows all global rules that are appliciable to all of our other servers. You can find our global rules on our wiki and at /spawn.
As an important note, do not build a one chunk bases or farms. ShadowNode staff will take action as required.</description></item><item><title>Offensive Skins</title><link>/home/guides/skins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/skins/</guid><description>Offensive Skins If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance that you&amp;rsquo;ve been hit with a ban that says &amp;ldquo;Your skin is offensive, please change it&amp;rdquo;. You forgot to change your Hitler skin when you were trolling, don&amp;rsquo;t worry! Even though you&amp;rsquo;ve quickly changed it, you still lost valuable playing time.
Don&amp;rsquo;t want that to happen to you? Just do one quick thing: Check your skin! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t changed it in a while, it might be good to take a quick look in game by using F5 or a site like NameMC.</description></item><item><title>Prism</title><link>/join/prism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/join/prism/</guid><description>Prism Launcher Prism is a third-party launcher not related to Microsoft, Mojang, CurseForge, FTB. It can be used to launch vanilla Minecraft, custom Modpacks, FTB, and CurseForge Modpacks. This launcher is great for getting into modded Minecraft and providing a simple experience but also caters to power users. Prism run on Windows, Linux, and macOS.
How to Install Head to Prism Launcher and download the Prism Launcher for your OS. The steps below are taken from a Windows install so it might be different if you&amp;rsquo;re on macOS or Linux.</description></item><item><title>Project Ozone 3</title><link>/modpack-tips/poz3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/poz3/</guid><description>Note This list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knowledge.
Important Rules Our Project Ozone 3 server has some additional rules on the server apart from the global rules you find on all our servers.
Up to 2 Imaginary Time Blocks per area Up to 2 Growth Crystals per area Up to 2 Fluid Cows of each type per area Giving away creative or end game items is not allowed.</description></item><item><title>Ranks</title><link>/server-info/ranks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/ranks/</guid><description>Available Ranks On the server we have multiple ranks that you can contribute to acquire.
The first few include some commands with many being useful and some fun ones included with a few.
Also, every rank inherits the commands/features from the previous ranks. Price of each rank is also located on the shop page.
Note All ranks have access to their specific prefix in /perks. Meaning if you have example eclipse rank you may use the prefix Member/Shade/Night/Equinox/Eclipse (like hide your rank or use another).</description></item><item><title>Relocate</title><link>/home/guides/relocate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/relocate/</guid><description>Relocation Crate relocation is a method that we have created in order to compensate for wiping servers. it will hold a limited number of items for you to be able to access them later.
Conditions to be capable of relocating Must be across servers with the same mod pack, such as Stoneblock A to Stoneblock B May also be used to store some items to use after a map wipe Cannot be across different mod packs, such as Skyfactory to Beyond If you run /relocate a message in chat will be triggered to warn you of a few common issues:</description></item><item><title>Rules and Policies</title><link>/server-info/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/rules/</guid><description>ShadowNode was created in 2014 by our owner ShadowKitten. Aiming to provide players with the best experience possible, ShadowNode is proud to host over 10 diverse servers!
Rules These rules apply to our Discord, servers and all other services. By using our services, you are agreeing to follow these rules. Ignorance of these rules is not an excuse. Staff are provided with a general guideline of punishments for each rule, however choosing a punishment is at their discretion.</description></item><item><title>Servers</title><link>/server-info/server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/server/</guid><description> Loading
Pack: Pack Version: Players: Uptime: Click to copy ip! This Week: Todays Record: Weekly Record: Monthly Record: Staff last seen:</description></item><item><title>Skyfactory 3</title><link>/legacy/modpack-tips/skyfactory3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/legacy/modpack-tips/skyfactory3/</guid><description>Note This list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our Skyfactory 3 server follows all global rules that are appliciable to all of our other servers and has a couple additional rules. You can find our global rules on our wiki and at /spawn.
You can have a max of 4 of each chicken.</description></item><item><title>Skyfactory 4</title><link>/modpack-tips/skyfactory4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/skyfactory4/</guid><description>Note This list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our Skyfactory 4 server has some additional rules on the server apart from the general rules you find on all our servers.
Max of 2 Hopping Bonsai Pot per sappling type per island. Truffles drop as an item. Ensure you collect them properly. As an improtant note, do not build a 1 chunk bases or farms.</description></item><item><title>Summoning the Ender Dragon</title><link>/home/guides/enderdragon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/enderdragon/</guid><description>Summoning the Ender Dragon Note This information has been depreciated and you should be able to spawn the dragon with just the 4 end crystals as per normal.
To summon the Ender Dragon, you will need 43 blocks of obsidian in your inventory and 4 end crystals. Simply go to The End, and run the command /portalplace with the required materials in your inventory. Once the structure is built, place the 4 end crystals on each side of the structure and the ender dragon should spawn!</description></item><item><title>Support</title><link>/server-info/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/support/</guid><description>Why Support Tickets Support tickets are a great way to ensure that your issue gets properly tracked and handled by the right team. In order to get a support ticket created you will need a few things.
Be in ShadowNode&amp;rsquo;s Discord Server. Have embeds enabled in Discord (this is on by default). Ability to talk / use our #tickets channel Creating a ticket Note In the examples below we&amp;rsquo;re looking at a locked ticket, however, it&amp;rsquo;ll work similarly for any other ticket.</description></item><item><title>Teaming Up</title><link>/home/guides/team-play/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/team-play/</guid><description>Intro Some players like to play together with others and work as a group. As a result, they want to sync what ever is possible to avoid doing double the work. Please keep in mind that our staff are not here to solve intergroup issues such a team member &amp;ldquo;stealing&amp;rdquo;.
Area Commands Note This applies to most Sky blocks style packs like FTB Skyfactory 3 and FTB StoneBlock 2.
Follow these steps to invite someone to your existing area.</description></item><item><title>The Store</title><link>/home/guides/store/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/store/</guid><description>The store is a place where you can purchase upgrades to support us, besides using the voting system. Note All money received is used to improve our network for its users who may or may not to choose to support us via the store or even through voting. Please make sure you have your parents permission to purchase upgrades on our stores if you&amp;rsquo;re one of our younger users.
Overview Top Right Corner This little widget shows how much you currently have in your &amp;ldquo;Shopping Cart&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Vote</title><link>/server-info/vote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/vote/</guid><description>Earn tokens by voting here FTB Servers Minecraft-MP Why Vote Voting increases our rank and reputation on voting websites. This can result in new players joining. The tokens you get from voting are a global form of currency which you can trade in for rewards. We have a monthly giveaway of Steam Game Keys for permanent copies of certain games for the Top 3 Voters! More details can be found on our Wiki entry about voting and rewards The Voting System We have 2 voting website we are listed on.</description></item><item><title>Voting</title><link>/home/guides/voting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/voting/</guid><description>The Voting System Our voting system is relatively simple and easy to understand.
We have 2 voting website we are listed on. Each of which you can use to vote on, once per day. You vote by filling in your Minecraft username in the text window and completing the Captcha. Voting gives you 100 Tokens per voting website, which can be used for in-game items or transactions with other users. Why should you vote?</description></item><item><title>What are Java Args</title><link>/home/guides/java-args/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/java-args/</guid><description>Java Args are a way to direct java as a program on how to handle a Modpack on how to handle itself the best. We have a few recommended Java arguments for specific packs, however, they should work for any pack in general.
We always recommend having at least 1.5GB to 2GB of RAM left over for your computer to perform normal tasks outside of Minecraft to ensure that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t cause crashes.</description></item><item><title>What Java To Use</title><link>/home/guides/java-versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/java-versions/</guid><description>With the release of Minecraft 1.18 we now have 3 different versions of Java that we need to have installed if we want to access all that Minecraft currently has to offer.
Warning We recommend reading the entire post as you might get an incorrect download otherwise.
In short, you need the following versions of Java for the related versions of Minecraft. Please note that downloading from the Oracle Archive you&amp;rsquo;ll need to sign up for an Oracle Account.</description></item><item><title>Wipes and Restarts</title><link>/server-info/wipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/wipes/</guid><description>Servers restart every once in a while to reduce lag. This does not mean that a restart will fix all kinds of lag. So, please, do not ask staff to restart a server due to lag. Restarts are NOT wipes, they are just a scheduled reboot to the server.
Ground items are cleared every 20 minutes (XX:10, XX:30, XX:50). There is a 1 minute warning before a clear.
Note All times listed are in Eastern Standard Time (EST).</description></item></channel></rss>