<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Launchers on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>/home/launchers/</link><description>Recent content in Launchers on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/home/launchers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ATLauncher</title><link>/home/launchers/atlauncher/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/launchers/atlauncher/</guid><description>About ATLauncher How to Install Head to ATLauncher and select which software is most appropriate for you. Typically for Windows you want to click the &amp;ldquo;Setup (Recommended)&amp;rdquo; button. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve opened the downloaded file please follow these directons. Please note that they were written on a Windows Machine and may differ depending on you Windows version or OS.
Click next Accept the license agreement, click next. Choose your install directory and click next.</description></item><item><title>CurseForge</title><link>/home/launchers/curseforge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/launchers/curseforge/</guid><description>CurseForge CurseForge is a popular Minecraft launcher. It can be used to launch vanilla Minecraft, custom Modpacks, or CurseForge Modpacks. This launcher great for getting into modded Minecraft and providing a simple expirence. However, for advanced users we&amp;rsquo;d recommend using GDLauncher or MultiMC. CurseForge works on Windows and macOS.
How to Install Head to CurseForge and download the CurseForge Beta Launcher for your OS. The steps below are taken from a Windows install so it might be different if you&amp;rsquo;re on macOS.</description></item><item><title>FTB App</title><link>/home/launchers/ftbapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/launchers/ftbapp/</guid><description>About FTB App FTB App is a popular Minecraft launcher brought to you by the Feed The Beast Team. It can be used to launch vanilla Minecraft, Feed The Beast (FTB), or CurseForge modpacks. This launcher great for getting into modded Minecraft and providing a simple expirence. However, for advanced users we&amp;rsquo;d recommend using GDLauncher or MultiMC. FTB App works on Windows, Linux and macOS.
How to Install Head to Feed The Beast and click on the download link for your platform.</description></item><item><title>GDLauncher</title><link>/home/launchers/gdlauncher/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/launchers/gdlauncher/</guid><description>About GDLauncher GDLauncher is a Minecraft launcher. It can be used to launch vanilla Minecraft, custom modpacks, or regular modpacks. This launcher is one of our recommended options for installing modpacks and managing mods. GDLauncher works on all major platforms - Windows, Linux and macOS.
How to Install Head to GDevs and select which software is most appropriate for you. Typically you want to click the &amp;ldquo;Download Now!&amp;rdquo; button. Click the download link related to your OS and then save it to your Downloads folder for easy access.</description></item><item><title>MultiMC</title><link>/home/launchers/multimc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/launchers/multimc/</guid><description>About MultiMC MultiMC is a Minecraft launcher. It can be used to launch vanilla Minecraft, custom modpacks, or regular modpacks. The launcher is very good for Linux users or those who don&amp;rsquo;t like the Twitch Launcher. We strongly recommend this launcher.
How to Install NotePlease note that you should not attempt to run the program from within the zip file. You will need to extract it first.
Head to MultiMC and select which software is most appropriate for you.</description></item></channel></rss>