<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guides on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>/home/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Guides on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/home/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advanced Claim Management</title><link>/home/guides/advancedclaims/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/advancedclaims/</guid><description>Public Transit Within Claims Viaducts and Waystones are a great and fun way to get around an expansive base while not forcing the use of homes and teleportation requests to other friends and basemates! That being said, typically you would need to give them full access to inventories such as your chests, crates, ME systems, etc. You can solve this by issuing some commands that will set &amp;ldquo;flags&amp;rdquo;, these are extra settings that override the default behavior.</description></item><item><title>Chunkloaders</title><link>/home/guides/chunkloaders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/chunkloaders/</guid><description>Chunk Loaders Modded Chunk Loaders have been disabled on ShadowNode servers globally, therefore we have added a plugin known as Better Chunk Loaders to achieve their purpose. There are two types of Chunk Loaders, Always On and Online Only. To view chunk borders, hit F3+g
Always On vs Online Only Always On is a chunk loader which is online 24/7 and will keep the chunk loaded. However, the chunk loader will stop loading the chunk after 48 (1.</description></item><item><title>Claiming</title><link>/home/guides/claiming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/claiming/</guid><description>Claiming All of our servers use the latest Grief Prevention plugin for claiming.
How to Claim To claim you can either use a Golden Shovel you make, or one provide to you when you first join the server (some servers do not start with the golden shovel or have had their claim tool changed). Every block claimed is accounted for. You can buy claim blocks from the tokenshop, or from the store.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>/home/guides/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/contributing/</guid><description>Intro You might want to contribute code, content or time to this wiki and are unsure how to do so. Please follow the steps below on how to do so.
NoteAll of these sections mentioning GitHub require a GitHub account!
Making Suggestions for Edits If you&amp;rsquo;re not comfortable writing Markdown or using Git you can make suggestions for edits via our project&amp;rsquo;s GitHub Issues or open a ticket in our Discord detailing the changes needed.</description></item><item><title>Crash Reports</title><link>/home/guides/crash-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/crash-reports/</guid><description>NoteThis page is still a work in progress and has yet to be finished!
Here you will find how to get your crash report for your specific launcher of choice.
FTB Launcher Open the Launcher Select the Modpack, click on Edit Modpack and on Open Folder. Now you are in the mods folder, go back to the minecraft folder. Open the crash-reports folder. Paste the content of the latest crash-report MCLo.</description></item><item><title>Crates</title><link>/home/guides/crates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/crates/</guid><description>Crates We use a plugin called HuskyCrates to manage our crates. Crates contain items, the quality of which depends on the tier of the crate. To open a create you must hold the crate key in your hand and right click the corresponding crate. You can obtain crate keys by either purchasing them from our shop, or buy buying them in our token shop. NoteSome items on this list may not be on your server as some modpacks don&amp;rsquo;t have all the mods as others.</description></item><item><title>Github Gist</title><link>/home/guides/gist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/gist/</guid><description>How to Use Github Gist While other copy and paste tools, like Pastebin or Hastebin, are more popular then Github Gist, Github Gist is one of the better copy and paste tools. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a character count and it&amp;rsquo;s just as easy to use as other tools. Using a copy and paste tool like Gist is recommended if you have issues with client crashes since it keeps the formatting of the log, and makes it easier to read the file without having to download it.</description></item><item><title>Managing Mods</title><link>/home/guides/managing-mods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/managing-mods/</guid><description>Managing Your Mods WarningRemoving and adding mods can cause pack instablity. Please consult your launcher&amp;rsquo;s documentation on backing up your instance prior to preforming any of the tips below.
Modded Minecraft is great and there&amp;rsquo;s tons of mods you likely have in your modpacks you play every day and are unaware of. In fact, there&amp;rsquo;s often a few bundled mods in packs that simply add bloat, don&amp;rsquo;t provide any functionality to the end user and in the end are simply unnecessary to play the pack.</description></item><item><title>Market</title><link>/home/guides/market/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/market/</guid><description>The Market Our market plugin is a custom plugin created by our owner, ShadowKitten. Running /market help in game will return a list of commands.
How to Access the Market To view the current listings, type the command /market How to buy an item You can either browse the market or you can click on the Search Seller button to find a specific player&amp;rsquo;s listening. Once you click on search, /market search seller &amp;lt;seller&amp;gt; will show up in your chat.</description></item><item><title>Offensive Skins</title><link>/home/guides/skins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/skins/</guid><description>Offensive Skins If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance that you&amp;rsquo;ve been hit with a ban that says &amp;ldquo;Your skin is offensive, please change it&amp;rdquo;. You forgot to change your Hitler skin when you were trolling, don&amp;rsquo;t worry! Even though you&amp;rsquo;ve quickly changed it, you still lost valuable playing time.
Don&amp;rsquo;t want that to happen to you? Just do one quick thing: Check your skin! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t changed it in a while, it might be good to take a quick look in game by using F5 or a site like NameMC.</description></item><item><title>Relocate</title><link>/home/guides/relocate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/relocate/</guid><description>Relocation Crate relocation is a method that we have created in order to compensate for wiping servers. it will hold a limited number of items for you to be able to access them later.
Conditions to be capable of relocating Must be across servers with the same mod pack, such as Stoneblock A to Stoneblock B May also be used to store some items to use after a map wipe Cannot be across different mod packs, such as Skyfactory to Beyond If you run /relocate a message in chat will be triggered to warn you of a few common issues:</description></item><item><title>Summoning the Ender Dragon</title><link>/home/guides/enderdragon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/enderdragon/</guid><description>Summoning the Ender Dragon NoteThis information has been depreciated and you should be able to spawn the dragon with just the 4 end crystals as per normal.
To summon the Ender Dragon, you will need 43 blocks of obsidian in your inventory and 4 end crystals. Simply go to The End, and run the command /portalplace with the required materials in your inventory. Once the structure is built, place the 4 end crystals on each side of the structure and the ender dragon should spawn!</description></item><item><title>Teaming Up</title><link>/home/guides/team-play/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/team-play/</guid><description>Intro Some players like to play together with others and work as a group. As a result, they want to sync what ever is possible to avoid doing double the work. Please keep in mind that our staff are not here to solve intergroup issues such a team member &amp;ldquo;stealing&amp;rdquo;.
Area Commands NoteThis applies to most Sky blocks style packs like FTB Skyfactory 3 and FTB StoneBlock 2.
Follow these steps to invite someone to your existing area.</description></item><item><title>The Store</title><link>/home/guides/store/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/store/</guid><description>The store is a place where you can purchase upgrades to support us, besides using the voting system. NoteAll money received is used to improve our network for its users who may or may not to choose to support us via the store or even through voting. Please make sure you have your parents permission to purchase upgrades on our stores if you&amp;rsquo;re one of our younger users.
Overview Top Right Corner This little widget shows how much you currently have in your &amp;ldquo;Shopping Cart&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Voting</title><link>/home/guides/voting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/voting/</guid><description>The Voting System Our voting system is relatively simple and easy to understand.
We have 2 voting website we are listed on. Each of which you can use to vote on, once per day. You vote by filling in your Minecraft username in the text window and completing the Captcha. Voting gives you 100 Tokens per voting website, which can be used for in-game items or transactions with other users.</description></item><item><title>What are Java Args</title><link>/home/guides/java-args/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/java-args/</guid><description>Java Args are a way to direct java as a program on how to handle a Modpack on how to handle itself the best. We have a few recommended Java arguments for specific packs, however, they should work for any pack in general.
We always recommend having at least 1.5GB to 2GB of RAM left over for your computer to perform normal tasks outside of Minecraft to ensure that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t cause crashes.</description></item><item><title>What Java To Use</title><link>/home/guides/java-versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/home/guides/java-versions/</guid><description>With the release of Minecraft 1.18 we now have 3 different versions of Java that we need to have installed if we want to access all that Minecraft currently has to offer.
WarningWe recommend reading the entire post as you might get an incorrect download otherwise.
In short, you need the following versions of Java for the related versions of Minecraft. Please note that downloading from the Oracle Archive you&amp;rsquo;ll need to sign up for an Oracle Account.</description></item></channel></rss>