<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Server Info on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/</link><description>Recent content in Server Info on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Banned Items</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/banned/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/banned/</guid><description>We have banned certain items on our servers because of issues in the past that now require us to disable them. If you encounter a bug, or any issue with the items, please report it in our Discord Support channel. Our plugin allows us to ban the items in a way that allows you to still progress through the pack. Craft, Place, Use, and Near are all the different ways items can be banned.</description></item><item><title>Ranks</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/ranks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/ranks/</guid><description>Available Ranks On the server we have multiple ranks that you can contribute to acquire.
The first few include some commands with many being useful and some fun ones included with a few.
Each rank also has their own custom join/leave message.
Also every rank inherits the commands/features from the previous ranks.
Price of each rank is also located on the contribute page.
NoteAll ranks have access to their specific prefix in /perks.</description></item><item><title>Rules and Policies</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/rules/</guid><description>ShadowNode was created in 2014 by our owner ShadowKitten. Aiming to provide players with the best experience possible, ShadowNode is proud to host over 15 diverse servers!
Rules These rules apply to our Discord, servers and all other services. By using our services, you are agreeing to follow these rules. Ignorance of these rules is not an excuse. Staff are provided with a general guideline of punishments for each rule, however choose a punishment is at their discretion.</description></item><item><title>Servers</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/server/</guid><description>Loading
Pack: Pack Version: Players: Uptime: Click to copy ip! This Week: Todays Record: Weekly Record: Monthly Record: Staff last seen:</description></item><item><title>Staff</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/staff/</guid><description>Position Name(s) Owner ShadowKitten Senior Administrator Aaron8059(A) Babymillie Dnsmasq RedSensei(A) War_Horse Endercorps_Alpha Administrator Cosmic_Elemental InkEyes Moody_420 Zyion Moderator Apollo Radicaljim ItsAFauxyKitty hachiimann ItsNora_ PopularSean LethalMrM Developer Bennyboy1695 YourMCGeek Babymillie Builders neoneix ItsNora_ Skull Lady Malady ItsAFauxyKitty MIT InfernalShadow neoneix NoteMembers with (A) behind there name are in Away mode.</description></item><item><title>Vote</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/vote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/server-info/vote/</guid><description>Earn tokens by voting here FTB Servers Minecraft-MP Voting helps ShadowNode grow, gain new players and also expand. If you want to use your tokens you can do so via using the in-game command /tokenshop.
Every month we give away free games to the top 3 voters of the month!</description></item></channel></rss>