<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Server Info on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>/server-info/</link><description>Recent content in Server Info on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/server-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Banned Items</title><link>/server-info/banned/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/banned/</guid><description>We have banned certain items on our servers because of issues in the past that now require us to disable them. If you encounter a bug, or any issue with the items, please report it in our Discord Support channel. Our plugin allows us to ban the items in a way that allows you to still progress through the pack. Craft, Place, Use, and Near are all the different ways items can be banned.</description></item><item><title>Ranks</title><link>/server-info/ranks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/ranks/</guid><description>Available Ranks On the server we have multiple ranks that you can contribute to acquire.
The first few include some commands with many being useful and some fun ones included with a few.
Each rank also has their own custom join/leave message.
Also, every rank inherits the commands/features from the previous ranks. Price of each rank is also located on the shop page.
NoteAll ranks have access to their specific prefix in /perks.</description></item><item><title>Rules and Policies</title><link>/server-info/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/rules/</guid><description>ShadowNode was created in 2014 by our owner ShadowKitten. Aiming to provide players with the best experience possible, ShadowNode is proud to host over 15 diverse servers!
Rules These rules apply to our Discord, servers and all other services. By using our services, you are agreeing to follow these rules. Ignorance of these rules is not an excuse. Staff are provided with a general guideline of punishments for each rule, however choose a punishment is at their discretion.</description></item><item><title>Servers</title><link>/server-info/server/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/server/</guid><description>Loading
Pack: Pack Version: Players: Uptime: Click to copy ip! This Week: Todays Record: Weekly Record: Monthly Record: Staff last seen:</description></item><item><title>Staff</title><link>/server-info/staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/staff/</guid><description> NoteMembers with (A) behind there name are in Away mode. They may or may not be able to assist.
For quick help, #support or a #tickets is still the best way to get support. Provided you have joined ShadowNode Discord.
You will need to be in the ShadowNode Discord to message staff or create a ticket.</description></item><item><title>Vote</title><link>/server-info/vote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/vote/</guid><description>Earn tokens by voting here FTB Servers Minecraft-MP Why Vote Voting increases our rank and reputation on voting websites. This can result in new players joining. The tokens you get from voting are a global form of currency which you can trade in for rewards.</description></item><item><title>Wipes and Restarts</title><link>/server-info/wipes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/server-info/wipes/</guid><description>Servers restart every once in a while to reduce lag. This does not mean that a restart will fix all kinds of lag so, please, do not as staff to restart a server due to lag. Restarts are NOT wipes, they are just a scheduled reboot to the server.
Ground items are cleared every 20 minutes (XX:10, XX:30, XX:50). There is a 1 minute warning before a clear.
NoteAll times listed are in Eastern Standard Time (EST).</description></item></channel></rss>