<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Modpack Tips on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>/modpack-tips/</link><description>Recent content in Modpack Tips on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/modpack-tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1.16 Packs</title><link>/modpack-tips/1-16_packs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/1-16_packs/</guid><description>NoteThis section might not always be up-to-date. Please let us know or submit changes if you discover this is the case. To find out how see contributing.
1.16 vs 1.12 Packs Many of you are already familiar with 1.12.2 and 1.16 packs but there are some key changes that seemingly impact all 1.16 packs as a whole. As a result of this you&amp;rsquo;re likely wondering what&amp;rsquo;s changed and how you can work around it.</description></item><item><title>ATM6 Sky</title><link>/modpack-tips/atm6sky/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/atm6sky/</guid><description>NoteThis page is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Should you find it needs an update please either let us know on Discord or consider contributing to our wiki directly.
Important Rules Our OceanBlock server follows all global rules that are applicable to all of our other servers. You can find our global rules on our wiki and at /spawn.</description></item><item><title>FTB Oceanblock</title><link>/modpack-tips/ftb_oceanblock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/ftb_oceanblock/</guid><description>Important Rules Our OceanBlock server follows all global rules that are applicable to all of our other servers. You can find our global rules on our wiki and at /spawn.
As an important note, do not build a 1 chunk bases or farms. ShadowNode staff will take action as required. Staff response will depend on the situation.
Getting Started If you&amp;rsquo;ve never played on ShadowNode&amp;rsquo;s OceanBlock server, the way you get started is to run /is create.</description></item><item><title>FTB Stoneblock 2</title><link>/modpack-tips/stoneblock2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/stoneblock2/</guid><description>NoteThis list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our Stoneblock 2 server has some additional rules on the server apart from the global rules you find on all our servers.
Max 2 Imaginary Time Blocks. This applies per team/base/area. Max 2 Growth Crystals. This applies per team/base/area. Cows and Chickens Cows and Chickens must always be in their respective pens.</description></item><item><title>MC Eternal</title><link>/modpack-tips/mc-eternal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/mc-eternal/</guid><description>NoteThis list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our MC Eternal server follows all global rules that are appliciable to all of our other servers. You can find our global rules on our wiki and at /spawn.
As an improtant note, do not build a 1 chunk bases or farms. ShadowNode staff will take action as required.</description></item><item><title>Project Ozone 3</title><link>/modpack-tips/poz3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/poz3/</guid><description>NoteThis list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knowledge.
Important Rules Our Project Ozone 3 server has some additional rules on the server apart from the global rules you find on all our servers.
Up to 2 Imaginary Time Blocks per area Up to 2 Growth Crystals per area Up to 2 Fluid Cows of each type per area Giving away creative or end game items is not allowed.</description></item><item><title>Skyfactory 3</title><link>/modpack-tips/skyfactory3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/skyfactory3/</guid><description>NoteThis list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our Skyfactory 3 server follows all global rules that are appliciable to all of our other servers and has a couple additional rules. You can find our global rules on our wiki and at /spawn.
You can have a max of 4 of each chicken.</description></item><item><title>Skyfactory 4</title><link>/modpack-tips/skyfactory4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modpack-tips/skyfactory4/</guid><description>NoteThis list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Important Rules Our Skyfactory 4 server has some additional rules on the server apart from the general rules you find on all our servers.
Max of 2 Hopping Bonsai Pot per sappling type per island. Truffles drop as an item. Ensure you collect them properly.</description></item></channel></rss>