<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Modpack Tips on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/modpack-tips/</link><description>Recent content in Modpack Tips on ShadowNode Modded Game Servers</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://beta.shadownode.ca/modpack-tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FTB Oceanblock Tips</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/modpack-tips/ftb_oceanblock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/modpack-tips/ftb_oceanblock/</guid><description>Known Issues This list is current as of the time of writing this but might not always be up-to-date. Take advice here with that knoweldge.
Below is a current list of known issues with Ocean Block and work arounds (if any)
Joining an Island Wipes Inventory and Progress Currently if you join a team or island after you're already started the game you will lose all of your currently unlocked quest progress as well as having everything in your inventory wiped.</description></item><item><title>MC Eternal Tips</title><link>https://beta.shadownode.ca/modpack-tips/mc-eternal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://beta.shadownode.ca/modpack-tips/mc-eternal/</guid><description>Recommended Java Arguments Eternal is a heavier pack and tends to use a lot of RAM and resources we have compiled a list of suggested arugments from the pack's Discord server and are adding them here for ease of use.
6.5GB -&amp;gt; 8GB of RAM allocated to Eternal Please use the following arguments -XX:+UseConcMarkSweepGC -XX:+UseParNewGC -XX:MaxNewSize=2000m -XX:+DisableExplicitGC -XX:SurvivorRatio=1 -XX:InitialSurvivorRatio=1 -XX:NewRatio=2 9GB+ of RAM allocated to Eternal Please use the following arguments XX:MaxNewSize=1800m -XX:+DisableExplicitGC -XX:SurvivorRatio=1 -XX:InitialSurvivorRatio=1 -XX:NewRatio=2 Disable Agricraft Particles A lot of players use Agricraft as way to enchance the speed at which their crops grow.</description></item></channel></rss>